The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
100 years ago
A hundred years ago,
the day when Red Butterfly was born,
Xue Yue witnessed a rare phenomenon of heaven and earth.
Five elemental spirits appeared.
They all gathered around the newborn Red Butterfly
and pledged to protect her for life.
As Red Butterfly grew up,
the strength of her elemental spirits increased.
Such a genius
was a blessing for Xue Yue.
I took Red Butterfly as my disciple
in order to investigate the origin of the elemental spirits.
But through divination,
I foresaw that Red Butterfly
will soon encounter a death disaster.
The night before
Xue Yue attacks
the Four Sect Alliance
Qing He,
in this battle,
Chong Ying\NXue Yue\NLate stage Soul Formation
you will take Red Butterfly's elemental spirits
and lead our army
in the Four Sect Alliance's territory.
Master...
Qing He\NXue Yue\NLate stage Soul Formation
The other day,
red mist envelopped my old body
as I predicted that Red Butterfly's death
will happen in this war.
If you cannot help her overcome her fate,
Red Butterfly will be dead by the end of the war.
That way, in the future,
she will be safe.
Master...
Red Butterfly has only been with you for 100 years.
But I...
I am your first disciple !
Master !
What's wrong ?
This last divination spell
has exhausted my remaining lifespan.
But I had no other choice...
Qing He,
don't blame your Master.
Xue Yu has been trapped in this barren land
for far too long.
You are now the Elder Sister of Xue Yue.
Protecting Red Butterfly
also means
protecting our Xue Yue.
The future...
Master !
Master !!
Master !!!
Master...
Disciple
accepts your order.
Go, go faster !
You monsters, get wrecked !
Lord Envoy,
the country of Suzaku promised
that they would help me once.
So now...
Please kill this Azure Dragon !
She's alive ?!
I have no right to kill this dragon.
Ou Zhi\NEnvoy of the country of Suzaku \NEarly stage Soul Transformation
Soul Transformation ?!
But taking out his blood
to stop him from causing trouble,
that is something I can do.
I turns out our opponent
has never been Red Butterfly...
but the country of Suzaku...
From now on,
you won't have to worry about this dragon.
The Guardian Azure Dragon... has lost.
Get out of the way !
Go ! Quick !
With the fall of the Guardian Azure Dragon,
the Four Sect Alliance has lost.
The outcome of the war is certain.
Five spirits,
attack !
One is missing ?
Zhou Yun !
Elder !
Fortunately, the Heaven Defying Bead can absorb elemental spirits.
Otherwise, I'd have no way to survive.
Zhou Wutai just left the battlefield...
This is my only chance to get the Rain Cauldron.
This domain...
I didn't expect to see you here,
Brother Wang.
This Rain Cauldron is too precious
for me to hold.
It's too precious for our Four Sect Alliance.
If you want it, you can take it.
But whether you can keep it
will depend on your own luck.
Take one pill per day
and you will recover.
With the Rain Cauldron in hand,
I have to get out of here.
This is bad !
The remnants of the Four Sect Alliance,
Lian Ning \NXue Yue Elder\NEarly stage Soul Formation
must die !
Explode !
I won't let you leave !
Although she is Soul Formation,
her physical body is not necessarily strong.
With Ancient God blood,
I might have a chance.
This Nascent Soul puppet of yours
is pretty interesting.
Explode !
If I don't escape now,
it will only get harder in the future.
The only way to end this quickly
is a tribulation.
This is...
Divine Retribution !
How can a Nascent Soul brat
summon such a tribulation !?
Fall !
I am Ou Zhi from Suzaku.
Fellow cultivator, please summon the tribulation again !
I will reward you generously !
It really was Divine Retribution...
Fellow cultivator,
are you willing to show yourself ?
Killing this one Soul Formation
consumed all my artifacts.
I must not interfere
with the country of Suzaku.
The fall of the Guardian Azure Dragon
signed the end of the Four Sect Alliance.
The country was destroyed.
In the following years,
the remaining cultivators of the Four Sects Alliance almost all perished.
Those who survived
must hide their identity
in the new Xue Yue country
in order to survive.
5 years later
After absorbing the earth spirit,
the earth element has been completed.
Now the Heaven Defying Bead
has a bit of spiritual energy inside it.
These 5 elemental lights have hints of Life.
The Heaven Defying Bead
must have uses I have yet to discover.
I have to complete the 5 elements first.
Only then will the bead recognize me as its master
and maybe reveal its other powers.
To cultivate the Life and Death Domain,
the time alteration of the Heaven Defying Bead
is useless.
After 5 years, I cannot stay inside any longer.
I still need 4 years
before I can step into Soul Formation.
New Xue Yue
In just 5 years,
Xue Yue has developed to this point.
This is...
A death aura ?
There are many mortals here,
they should be brimming with life.
So why is this death aura so prevalent ?
Wang Lin only has a limited number of Void Ink Stones to craft Restriction Flags. Using a flag's tribulation if his last resort. Previously, he was hit by a tribulation and refined some Divine Retribution lightning by pure fluke. He used that lightning in episode 52 to attack Lin Yi, the Soul Formation envoy in Zhao.\NTrying to refine lightning once again would be completely crazy and a waste of ressources for Wang Lin.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.